<resources>
    <string name="app_name">RetroByte Blitz</string>
    <string name="activity_name">Daily Exercises</string>

    <!--    Category names-->
    <string name="category1_name">Logic</string>
    <string name="category2_name">Memory</string>
    <string name="category3_name">Calculation</string>
    <string name="category4_name">Visual</string>
    <string name="category5_name">Daily exercises</string>

    <!-- Instructions for games -->
    <string name="sudoku_instructions">Sudoku: Fill the Sudoku grid by placing numbers 1 to 9 in each row, column, and 3x3 sub-grid without repetition.</string>
    <string name="calculation_instructions">Calculation: Solve the mathematical expressions by performing the required calculations.</string>
    <string name="colors_instructions">Colors: Memorize the sequence of flashing colors and replicate it by pressing the corresponding buttons in the same order.</string>
    <string name="grid_instructions">Grid: Watch for the cells that light up. After they flash, click the same cells to clear the grid.</string>
    <string name="sequence_instructions">Sequence: Identify the pattern and complete the arithmetic or geometric sequence with the correct number.</string>
    <string name="number_of_instructions">Number of: Count the objects shown in the image and provide the correct total.</string>
    <string name="moving_sum_instructions">Moving Sum: Calculate the sum of a series of moving numbers.</string>
    <string name="descending_instructions">Descending: Arrange the items or images in descending order based on their appearance, including zero.</string>
    <string name="card_instructions">Cards: Find and match all the pairs of identical cards to complete the game.</string>
    <string name="slider_instructions">Slider: Rearrange the puzzle by swapping two pieces at a time to restore the original image. You can use the default image or upload your own.</string>
    <string name="stroop_instructions">Stroop: Click the button that corresponds to the color of the text, ignoring the meaning of the word.</string>
    <string name="roman_num_instructions">Roman Numerals: Match the Roman numerals to their equivalent Arabic numerals to form pairs.</string>

    <!-- Other UI strings -->
    <string name="today_date">Todays Date: %1$s</string>
    <string name="instructions_title">Instructions for %1$s</string>
    <string name="start_button">Start</string>
    <string name="no_instructions">No instructions available for this game.</string>
    <string name="daily_exercises_completed">Daily Exercises Completed!</string>
    <string name="completed_today">Return tomorrow</string>
    <string name="start_button_text">Start</string>
    <string name="leaderboard_date">Leaderboard for: %1$s</string>
    <string name="error_fetching_games">Error fetching daily games. Please try again later.</string>
    <string name="greeting">WELCOME</string>

</resources>